The Largo Sea.
Scattered throughout its beautiful waters
are throngs of islands,
most of which being unexplored,
shrouding the Sea in a veil of mystery.
But admist those isles lies bountiful paradise,
teeming with undiscovered
flora, fauna, and mineral deposits.
There, the shipwrecks of old are reclaimed by nature.
And right now, I'm enjoying
a little vacation here in those tropics.
If only that were true...
Get ready, whacky Demon Army racers!
Time to find out who's the fastest!
Ready, go!
Whoa, hold on!
Stop, Lily!
You little brat!
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Betrayed and left behind in this lonely world
Fearing a tomorrow I've lost sight of
I search for the place I belong
My heart screams out, "I want to be needed"
I want to puzzle out these entwined identities, but can I trust them?
Live, live on, with all your might
Follow the light to the future
Even if you lose everything
Stay connected to hope
I don't know why I'm here
But that's all right with me right now
I have to overcome and press on
So I can smile with you again
A Little Bit of Thought Goes A Long Way for Efficiency!
Lily is headed to Largo tomorrow on a logistics mission.
Largo? Why's she going that far out?
The Demon Army and the people of Largo
have a steadfast, unbreakable alliance.
Largo, huh... Land of the Dragonfolk, right?
About 3,000 years ago, Demon King Belial
led an attack on the human realm.
After his defeat, many denizens of
the Demon World found peace with humanity
and became a diverse part of their society.
Dragonfolk attempted to do the same,
but when humans began to aggressively persecute them,
it was clear coexistence was not an option.
So they went off to live in peace in the Largo Islands.
That's correct, and the dragonfolk still
remember that painful history, even now.
This was why they welcomed Queen Echidna's
invasion with open arms.
It's because of their stalwart support
and fervent assistance
that the Demon Army was able to continue
the fight against humanity for so long.
Largo is our army's lifeline.
Wow, I never knew.
Dragonfolk, damn... Not surprised
they're still holding that grudge.
Right. So you want me to head to Largo and
help out with the logistics mission, then?
Yes.
The castle's food and equipment stores are running low,
so we need to make sure this shipment comes in safe.
Yeah, that could be a serious issue.
And that's not the only problem.
Here's the mission plan Lily submitted to me...
Everyone's gonna have a big happy time!
For real?
Believe it or not, this is how ALL of her reports look.
Despite being entrusted with enough
manpower to carry out her mission,
it takes longer than usual for her to complete it...
So why're you sending me? Why not send Edvard?
He's dragonfolk himself, and from Largo.
He's gotta know stuff that can help.
We can't send him.
We need him to protect the palace.
Hey, I'll get that. And I'll get that one, too!
And the next one after that!
Plus, he'd end up doing everything himself.
Uh-huh...
Lily won't learn anything if he does all the work.
So you want me to go and keep an eye on her?
That's right.
Here I joined the Demon Army
to be stuck on babysitting duty...
If that's my job, I'll do it.
I want to get hired on permanently, after all.
Thanks, Leo.
You can use a warp portal to get to Largo...
Don't go missing me too much now, mmkay?
Please make preparations to leave as soon as possible!
Are we SURE she's a succubus?
Right, then.
I'm finally here in Largo...
Hey, Lily!
Cut it out!
Go, go!
STOP!
I win!
Congrats on getting second place!
Third and fourth did a real good job, too!
Lily, can we stop playing around now?
I'm not playing around!
What?
We were racing to see who could carry
the supplies the fastest!
Scuse me...
What's up?
We've got a whole lot more to transport.
That's fine!
We've only done one trip.
That's enough for today! Let's go eat!
Hey, Leo!
Here, take this, it'll make you feel better!
Down we go...
Say 'ahh'!
Thank you.
You're welcome!
There's no way we're finishing at this rate.
Largo has a warp portal between Largo
and the Demon Queen's palace,
and the isle's storage and logistics facilities
are brimming with supplies.
If the individual strengths of the isle's myriad
races were used effectively,
with the right person assigned for every job,
it would take a day, two days at the longest,
to get this job done.
If the right person were assigned
to the right  job, that is...
Hey, Leo, take one! It's yummy!
I-I'm good.
Then I'll go pass them out to everyone else!
Hey!
Here, have some carrots!
Thanks.
So... Who's that?
Huh? Oh, let me introduce you!
He's really cool, this is my future husband, L--
Black Knight Onyx! And we are NOT betrothed!
Everyone's invited to our wedd--
We're not having a wedding!
Ugh, fine! Force my hand, why don't you!
Excuse me, I need you to focus on these repairs...
Huh? The heck are you talkin' about?
Are you stupid? Any change in procedure
has to be signed off on by the boss.
The boss...
Dammit. I'm just a temp!
I can't do anything 'round here...
And the isle's inhabitants have lodged
dozens of complaints against us!
I'm sorry, I'm terribly sorry...
We can't apologize more for what we've done,
but I hope this helps a little...
If this keeps up, the resupply
will be the least of our worries.
We'll end up losing the dragonfolk and the logistics
center altogether!
And if that happens, then it's only a matter of time
before the Demon Army goes under!
I'm back!
Why the long face, Leo?
Are you feeling sick? Wanna eat this?
Wanna lay down?
My head hurts.
Oh, no!
I mean, metaphorically, not literally...
You need medicine! Does anyone have medicine?!
I need medicine!
She's such a sweet kid...
Does anyone around here have medicine?
It's an emergency!
Have the supplies from Largo arrived?
Not yet, ma'am...
I see.
Think the job's too big for the kid?
Lily is one of the Four Generals, just like us.
Besides...
Our forces, wiped out.
Half of our castle's facilities in ruins...
Yes, but thankfully, there wasn't a single casualty
in the battle against the Hero Leo.
Which means he was going easy on us.
We threw everything we had at him in that battle,
but it might as well have been nothing to him.
Your Demon Queen is an embarrassment to us all.
Your Highness...
Hey, Echidna!
I found this growing by the gate! It's a present for you!
Oh, hey! Let's plant a ton of flowers in the garden!
It'd look sooo pretty!
You're right. Thank you, Lily.
I'm sure Lily understands what to do.
I seriously hope so...
Does anyone have medicine?
I'll trade you this carrot for some medicine!
Someone, please, help...
I need some medicine for someone whose head hurts!
Sadly, she's still too immature.
I can't get through to her with logic like I would Shutina.
Leo's feeling really sick...
I'm glad she's so worried about me,
but I wish she'd spend half that energy--hell,
a tenth of that energy working instead of...
I've got it!
Hey, Leo!
I'm sorry it took so long.
I got you some medicine for your head...
Leo?
Does your head hurt?
I got bit by a snake...
Huh?!
That's a death viper!
You guessed it: I summoned this venomous viper,
and it's gonna help Lily mature.
No, Leo, stay with me!
It's the end of the line for me...
As powerful as I am, I'll be dead twelve hours from now...
No! I don't want you to die!
I know, Shutina can heal you!
She can't.
The warp portal's busted. We can't get back to the castle.
Huh?!
I made sure that nobody in the isles of Largo
had the skill to be able to heal me.
Which means there's only one other way to save my life...
Then I'll go and pick some medicine herbs!
Just like I wanted!
Please.
Some should be growing up on the western peaks...
Ugh, my vision's growing dark...
Hold on, I'll be right back!
Is west to the right or the left?
That way.
Got it!
The western peaks!
Cleanse.
That went well.
And all the trials I've prepped on the road
to the western peaks are ready.
To get through them, she'll need to manage
her people right and use the power of teamwork!
Yes, these trials were designed
to teach her how to manage a team!
It's the pinnacle of on-the-job training!
Herbs on the western peaks!
She's finally transformed into Fenrir, the Divine Wolf.
The Divine Wolf is a protective deity
on the continent of Erkia, Lily's home.
I have no idea why she's able to transform
into something that important.
Can anyone in her tribe do that, or is she just special?
There's only one thing I know for sure...
She's already reached the first trial.
I've cast an invincibility spell on this huge boulder
to nullify physical attacks.
Huh? Is this rock the kind you can't break?
To break through, she'll need to find
a subordinate who can remove the spell!
I can't break it...
Grr! I'm in a hurry, y'know!
Yes. That's right.
She'll figure it out soon: if she can't do something
herself, she can do it with a team.
And when she realizes that...
Oh, there it goes!
What?!
Little more! Little more!
A little more? Don't be stupid!
You're not supposed to force your way through!
Just give up and go to the nearest village!
A whole troop of spellcasters is stationed there!
You can run there in less than a minute!
Little more!
STOP!
She broke it. I can't believe it.
She did it by herself, without
any help from her underlings...
It's okay! She can't get through the second trial herself!
This time, it'll work!
Behold, infinitely replicating slimes!
Why are there more?!
Eww!
Amongst all those slimes is a single,
tiny slime: the core slime.
Take that one out, and the rest go with it.
The fastest way to get through the trial
is to bring over a perceptive underling...
She could even find someone who can cast ice magic.
I did it!
Halt!
A few more seconds, and you would
have been at the bottom of that cliff.
This is my third trial, a crevasse
I'd conjured up with gnomish power.
If she wants to get to the western peaks,
she'll need to find a way to get to the other side.
Who're you, mister?
Ah, my apologies. I am Godhart, a simple traveler.
I can't just sit back and watch!
I've concealed my smell, so she shouldn't know it's me!
Thanks!
See ya!
Even with Lily's impressive leaping ability,
she can't make that jump.
There's only one way...
Oh, how tragic!
If only I had a friend who could fly!
They could help me fly across the gap!
A friend... Could help?
Yes, when you can't solve a problem yourself,
you can solve it with the help of a friend!
Isn't that right?
Wow... Wow, yeah, you're right!
Okay, okay!
Thanks, Mister God! I'm gonna go ask everyone for help!
Take care.
Phew, good.
Had to get heavy-handed there,
but now she'll realize the importance of teamwork.
Now she just needs to put it into practice.
I'll make sure she gets all the practice she needs,
and cover for any mistakes...
I'll see to it that she grows into a fine leader.
Mister God!
I asked everyone for help, and they said
I can just swim across the bottom then climb up!
Look! Your advice helped me get
to the other side! Thanks!
Oh... Sure.
Another failure.
Another failure!
Come on, man...
Leo!
Lily?
Did you get the herbs?
Yep! You feeling better?
Uh, yeah. Real better. Thanks.
Yay!
Sheesh... Ignorance truly is bliss.
Oh, yeah! I wanna show you something!
Here.
Aww, you drew me a picture?
Wait...
Do you think we could work like this?
Did you think this up all by yourself?
Nope. Mister God-- uh, Godheart, came up with it.
He said it's way easier to work together
as a team than do something by yourself!
I thought a lot about it while you were sleeping.
I'm real stupid, so I won't figure
stuff out unless someone tells me!
I assumed you could tell her something
a hundred times and she wouldn't get it.
I thought the only way to get through to her
was by forcing her into the situation.
But I was wrong.
Hey, so, you think this'll make our work easier?
But in the end, I was the idiot, not Lily.
Maybe it won't work after all...
All I had to do was tell her "hey, maybe try this".
Yeah, this'll make it way easier.
Good job, Lily! Superb work.
Everyone was super happy to split up
the work and get it done faster!
I realized just how important it is to work as a team!
Our Beast General is on her way to
becoming quite the reliable leader.
I guess, though I could've done without
the whole mock wedding ceremony...
Why are you laughing? It's not funny.
So, what do you need me for today?
Oh, right. We've no time for small talk.
Leo, I have an important missive for you.
Let me guess, I'm being made a permanent employee?
It comes straight from Queen Echidna:
"Black Knight Onyx is to report to me at once."
What? Crap, did she catch on to me?!
Our hearts are always so frail and fragile
But we still face forward and continue down our long road
If we don't know something now, we can go learn about it
We might not know what's at the end of our long, continuing journey
Don't try to do everything yourself, lean on us sometimes
Sharing your weaknesses is strength in itself
There' still a long way to go, so make sure you won't regret anything
Dash on! The reason's simple
Let loose! Make your dreams reality
The future you're heading towards is one you shape yourself
It's okay to be scared of change, you can go little by little
I want to protect the things I cherish
(I'm so glad we found each other)
So I hope you hear how thankful I am for you
Next Time:
The Drinking
Party
From Hell